http://www.warrennolan.com/privacy/privacy

Effective: January 15, 2011
Fully Sports, FullySports.com, and WarrenNolan.com are strongly committed to protecting your privacy.
This Privacy Policy discloses how we collect, use and share information we gather about you on the Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com web sites.
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com web sites and not to any Advertisers or Ad Servering Networks that serve ads on our web sites.
We hope that this disclosure will enhance your experience on the Internet and reinforce the trust that you place in Fully Sports, Fullysports.com, and WarrenNolan.com services.
Information Collected Online
For each visitor to the Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com web sites, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name.
We do not collect the visitor's e-mail address.
We do collect aggregate information on what pages our visitors access while visiting Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com web sites.
The collected information is used to improve the content and performance of our web sites.
Cookies
Currently, we do not set any cookies.
Advertisers and Ad Serving Networks
Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com work with Google and other third parties to serve ads on our sites.
Some of these ads contain Cookies that are used to track user behavior.
This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of Cookies set by Google and other third parties advertisers.
Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com do not have control over, or even access to, the information contained in these third party Cookies.
For more information about how Google uses the information collected by these Cookies, please review Google's Privacy Policy.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Fullysports.com and WarrenNolan.com reserve the right to alter our Privacy Policy as business needs require.
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
All changes to this policy will be posted on our web sites prior to the time they take effect.
